The bone of my dear friend, the great Dio.
What the hell is this? The bone?
Where did it go?
I'm asking you where his bone
went, you best answer me!
I can feel the bone's presence at the
maximum security disciplinary wing,
right as we speak.
What?
Did Jolene make it so she
can go to the discipline
cell just to find that
same bone belonging to Dia?
Yeah, but it's way too reckless.
If I get my hands on it first, that
creepy palesnake will soon follow.
Also,
there's my father's stolen memory disk
that the bastard is still holding on to.
Where is that little guy?
I have to find him.
He's the one who's got the bone.
Now, where would he be hiding?
Before someone beats me there and knocks
him off, and I lose the bone forever.
No, I have to get it at all costs.
Wait what the no please
tell me this shit didn't
already happen please the
battle is already over.
They're all disfigured and bloated every
last body in this
discipline cell is fucked.
It's a stand power holy shit how
many stand users are in this place?
Were they the ones who did this?
And what exactly did they do?
But one user can have only one Stan power.
The person that defeated all the prisoners
here can only be one of
these two punks I see.
Obviously, they sent a shit ton more Stan
users to this ward than I assumed before.
At the very least,
there's still a Stan user
that stimulates the human
conscience and makes them
want to fight in here.
How can you stand with that gaping wound?
Your stand is intriguing, my dear.
A stand of string, who'd have thought?
I also find it interesting that your
combat moves are completely unpredictable.
Most interesting of all, however,
is your dogged determination.
It's obvious you've been gravely wounded,
but I can tell you've already grown
much from that brutal fight just now.
When Pale Snake told me that he'd send
four stand users here, including me,
I was taken aback, as
I'm sure you can imagine.
I thought of that many
necessary to accomplish this.
But now the reason why is totally obvious.
If he wants to eliminate you
for good, which he clearly does.
By the way, I am Kenzo,
a sprightly 78 years old.
The key to good health is
eight hours of deep sleep
and of course urine therapy
every day without fail
It's important to maintain good habits.
Are you familiar with it urine therapy?
If you want to play how gladly take
you on I can do it American style?
Or how about French style?
Japanese style work?
And of course, Italian Naples style.
All around the world, there's
a finger that says fuck you.
Thank you.
I'll get straight to the point, dear.
All the dead you see didn't
just die, they were drowned.
I drowned them,
that's why their bodies are bloated and
look like giant human
ticks about to explode.
And regrettably, it seems my
first opponent is not you.
Or at least not yet.
F .F., you're here!
Damn, they caught me moving in
the shadows of the bloated bodies.
I thought I had him.
So much for my Grand Kudomon.
Oh, how convenient.
A corpse somehow blocked my F .F.
bullets.
Yes, it was close indeed. Wait a sec.
How'd you get here, F .F.?
Don't worry about it.
But damn, I gotta say, it was
a pretty close call, Jolene.
And before you lose any more blood,
I'm gonna fill those wounds. Mm-hmm.
That guy.
Do I know him?
Oh yeah, I remember now.
I think I saw him with weather
forecast at Emporio's place.
But I have spun-finished business first.
I'm gonna take this creepy old geezer out.
and I'm going to like it!
Direction facing southeast.
127 degrees, 30 minutes, 20 seconds.
Sweat.
It's dripping down.
Are you going to open your mouth?
Would you prefer to drown, is that it?
What do you mean, drown?
I don't know what stupid plan you've
got, but actually, water is my jam.
If you think you can...
For a trained person to drown
under these circumstances,
it usually takes anywhere
between five to seven minutes.
But only if they draw breath deep
enough to leave oxygen in the lungs.
That's what binds them that precious time.
time.
If all the oxygen in
both lungs were exhaled,
that would have a far
less enjoyable outcome.
You see,
with only a few drops of water, a human
would just drown and then die instantly,
siphoned directly from your filthy mouth.
I damaged your fourth
cervical spine vertebrae.
There's a large nerve that
connects right to your kidney.
When one is under duress,
the adrenal glands secrete bodily fluid
into the respiratory
mucosa like a lubricant.
So From these few drops of water,
she'd evoke a feeling of being
suffocated by a giant wave. Lovely.
Oh my god, I can't breathe.
I'm inside a normal human's body.
Petro, I'm losing!
This is bad.
My body can't take it.
FF, no! No!
Do you want to drown too?
I'm glad to help out.
July, Cujo.
Huh?
Hiya!
What are you?
Identify yourself.
Are you a human?
Don't get up.
It's safer and wiser to
observe them from here.
What kind of stand user
is that old geezer anyway?
We should be evaluating his strengths
right now, wouldn't you say?
The main problem here, you see, is not the
old man's ability to drown other people,
But the fact that he dodged bullets...
Perhaps it's trite, but why aren't any
of the well-aimed shots hitting him?
That's a far more dangerous detail.
Why'd you come here?
And what was your name again?
Anastasia or something prissy?
Because I love you, and I've been
dying to see your face again.
Huh?
What did you just say?
That old man's been
locked up here a while.
He's served 40 years at this prison.
He's a lunatic who enjoys
drinking his own piss.
It had been ages since I'd
seen him in the men's ward.
It turned out he was here all along.
And now this decaying
freak show is a stand user.
In the fall of 1969, he
killed 34 young men and women.
He was sentenced to 280 years in prison.
The equivalent of several lifetimes.
That grinning gray carcass
was only 37 back then.
He claimed to be the
guru of a secret cult.
And he was so successful that he even had
hollywood stars in this
bizarre little fringe group.
But their activities led to issues between
his rabid followers and outside society.
So the police and fbi
started to get involved.
He knew he was fully cornered.
So he and 34 of His
followers holed up in a
Florida villa and planned
out a mass suicide.
But it wasn't quite that simple.
Kenzo drugged his followers
so they would pass out.
Then he set the building on fire.
You see all the believers burned to death,
except for one sole survivor who
just happened to be the cult leader.
It was just dumb luck, really.
Strangely,
it seems the wall of the
building nearest him collapsed in
such a way that partly shielded
him from the smoke and flames.
There is no doubt though that he was
indeed willing to die since he was near
death when they found him.
What's my point in telling you all this?
I'm sorry, I've digressed a bit,
but the fact is only he survived.
He'll never get released from
prison, but he wasn't
sentenced to death either.
This is the reality behind him.
I've never seen you before
and I don't know who you are,
but I can see your point of strength
as though you're made of glass,
the secret of the power
that lies within you.
It's patently clear that what
flows through every artery
in your body is very much
something other than blood.
Am I seeing the source
of your stand in action,
or is it a different organism entirely?
Either way, it will not affect
how I'm going to finish you off.
In terms of vital points
and body composition,
you're essentially no different
than a normal human being.
In the end,
you will shed Blood just
the same I assume by your
stance you're ready to drown
once again just be aware?
You won't survive this time West
Southwest 225 degrees zero minutes!
Yeah there it is put
something on his hand again
what the hell is that what's
with that weird slinky?
Oh, how utterly fascinating.
It seems your dragon's direction is...
Hey, FF, he's right behind you!
No, don't attack me.
You're just wasting your time. Truly!
You're just wasting your time. Truly.
I'm telling you, your real
enemy is that insane old man.
So stop shooting at me.
Don't you get it yet?
I'm impervious, an illusion.
Your attacks will only pass through me.
Eyes forward, danger approaches.
He's coming right at you!
I have no right to interfere.
It's only that old man.
He's your enemy.
Destroy him!
What is this?
The reason that old sack of shake
and dodge bullets is because of him?
Here he comes!
This guy is 78?
How does the Walking Dead
kick and punch so fast?
To quote a phrase, I can now
enter the dragon. Hi-yah!
What is he?
He tore his own arm off.
But why would he...
No way!
Now his arm is flying right
to the back of FF's head!
Shit, that was close.
But still, FF blocked
it! That was so Bites!
I noticed as soon as Kenzo
touched that dragon stand,
his arm disappeared in that same moment.
A smokescreen so he won't
see his attack coming.
Oh, shit.
Is that dragon behind him now?
When you touch it, does
your other arm tear off?
But just like the user,
the attack was weak!
No, FF.
This battle's result is already decided.
But it's not like anyone can actually
predict what happens, though.
Hiya!
And you, pipe down, you talk too much.
Why would you give away everything?
You're supposed to be
neutral, remember that.
You're operating in bad faith, though.
You must share your secret with her.
Oh, dear.
You opened your mouth.
Hi-ya!
FF, look out!
There is no freaking way
that was a coincidence.
That inmate's glasses flew straight at
FF and lodged themselves in their face?
Unfortunate direction.
Ah, I'm starting to understand.
It's feng shui in action.
It's geomancy for the East Asians.
Watch Kenzo's movement.
It's as if he's adjusting
to a certain direction.
Attacks coming from there.
One direction as if predetermined
and that stand on his hand.
It just works.
The only conclusion to be drawn is...
With that dragon stand, Kenzo can perfectly
control the direction of his attacks.
Feng shui?
What is that?
And what do you mean by direction?
I'll explain.
It's as famous as astrology
and tarot card reading,
maybe more, but it's not fortune-telling.
East Asian philosophy highlights the
idea that there are natural paths
of energy in the natural world
such as the flow of wind and water.
By knowing the direction
in which nature is flowing,
it helps people choose
similar paths for their lives.
Here's an example.
Feng Shui is used to determine the good
and bad areas of the land, house, and room.
If the direction of the
land or house is bad,
it will affect the
resident's health, fortune,
and even the whole family's
well-being negatively.
In times of war, it is said that they
checked the Feng Shui of the castle,
and thus could determine the
most advantageous area of the
fortress they could attack
from to bring down the enemy.
On the other hand, if you build a
shrine in the weak zone of the castle,
and can calm the evil energy,
the castle will gain a further
more solidified defense.
And of course, this same theory of feng
shui can also be applied to human bodies.
There's even an attack called
feng shui assassination.
If you can control the direction
from which to attack your enemy,
you're almost guaranteed
a victory over them.
No matter how alert and
prepared the target is,
you'll be able to approach
them without being noticed,
leaving them completely vulnerable,
and you can easily assassinate them.
That means...
Unlucky direction.
I think we've now established
the secret of Kenzo's stand.
The unlucky course pointing
straight toward FF.
That dragon stand is
pointing out the precise
direction for Kenzo to
kill them fast and easy.
And at some point very soon, his attack
will merge with that floating dragon.
I'm afraid FF's fate has
already been decided.
I can't believe Kenzo.
He spent the last 40 years in prison
mastering the Feng Shui assassination.
And that skill developed
as his stand power.
Feng Shui!
The direction to proceed!
Then that means, when he was on
defense, that would explain it.
That's why not one of the
bullets hit the old man either.
Unbelievable.
You're saying the feng shui also protected
him as well as helped
him try to kill them?
Yes, I am.
When he holds that dragon
stand in his hands,
he reads which direction
is the best to take.
And while moving in that direction,
he simultaneously launches his attack.
The dragon is trying to show the
direct line to kill again. FF, wait!
Those glasses were deliberately
made to shoot right into your face!
Hold the old man off!
Don't let him get too
close to that dragon!
I know.
It makes no fucking sense to me either.
But seriously, whatever you do, you
can't allow him to touch it! Let's go.
Nicely done, Drake's Dream.
Thank you.
They figured it out because you
had to go and flap your scaly jaws.
Shut up, you rotting mummy!
I'm not your henchman or your underling.
The art of feng shui belongs
to everyone, not just you.
But it's true that you can
utilize my power to the fullest.
FF, next unlucky spot is here,
right above your left ear. Feel it?
This direction has the utmost
critical emergency alert ringing.
Your lucky color is yellow, and your
charm is a picture of a goldfish,
if you have him.
Hey, look, he's going
around behind you, FF!
Time for a knife hand strike.
I don't even need to touch
the dragon's direction for it.
The movement of his defending
arm is also working as an attack.
Must be Tai Chi training.
How's your mouth?
I got you now!
Well, how?
If your defense works as an attack,
then the reverse applies too.
Turn about is fair play, old man. Hiya!
I've grown tired of this, you bitch.
I guess now I need to utilize the dragon's
direction to finish you off completely.
I forced your arm to
merge with the dragon.
How do you like that?
Just so you know, that's the same
move I employed in my attack before.
You're about to get beaten
senses by your very own arm.
Yes, that did just happen.
and my stand attack has merged
with the course of your death.
You asshole!
What the hell was that nightmare?
I lost my arm just then.
Are you responsible for that?
I told you there's an unlucky direction.
I'm very sorry.
That's caused by the
direction's certain power.
I have no way of knowing
what's gonna happen.
In the next moments, but
if I were you, young lady,
I would try my best to
prevent or minimize?
the inevitable damage.
Ah, Beth, hurry up and get out of there!
It's been destroyed by the meteor!
The fan's gonna fall on you!
Actually,
what you have to worry
about is not the fan,
it's the metal boomerang
heading I'm coming towards you!
Stop! Stop!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place
other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.